i am here to try to explain to you
my journey my stories but part of the
problem is when something happens it's
like 18 layers that come into it and 18
layers that go out of it
but i'm gonna try because
the video i shared last week it's really
long because it's the weave together of
the stories throughout the day where i
felt like because my kid's playdate
got cancelled and then i went for this
walk and the next morning the troll was
on the video and i was like this is a
monday in prophase a profound mundane
life like it's like
just learning as things come and then
because i went on that work on thursday
and i wrote this message to my siblings
who i don't really talk to my sister we
had one conversation we didn't talk for
a year and a half
uh we're kind of repairing what was
there before and and
without actually repairing it it's very
weird but um
i sent i had this urge to send the
message to my siblings i'm like okay
do it the universe told you to so i sent
this message to to my siblings on
facebook just about nathaniel the
greplit this is the christian
character it's in the video um and then
because of that
i had the messenger with my siblings
today we had to reschedule the playdate
for today
so while my kid was playing i was down
walking by the water
and i was
responding figuring out how to respond
to the woman on youtube i'm having a
conversation with
and arguing the mlm math and she's like
i'm building a business i have 1800
people under me this is this is
beautiful i don't know what you're
talking about why are you even
commenting on it because it's predatory
and i'm here to
take it down just so we're clear but
i had i was like i want to know how much
people actually spend on essential oil
right i'm going down this rabbit hole i
actually have a resource of somebody who
owns an essential oil company
why not ask them so i asked my sister
how much people spend on her
top end essential oils her business on
her website
and she was like eight eighty dollars is
like the average high end
i was like okay that makes that's okay
eighty dollars this is
high end high quality essential oil and
not just essential oil these are
products these are like
i own one of her i have one of her
deodorants and there's a bunch of other
stuff
um young livy i started young living
which one are we talking about
doterra is like you need to buy 150
worth of products
so because i was down and because we
cancelled the play date i was
on the walk later in the day signed up
with a sibling group therefore i felt
more comfortable
just asking the question didn't have
cell reception get the answer to later
but i was like i was like this is a
weird question to ask we're not really
connected right now i was like just see
like i was like i'm um researching
doterra and so that was the last message
she got for me and she was like don't
sign up for doterra they're a horrible
company
told me this story that they are a
horrible beyond what i do company
and then
oh i was like this is just so perfect
because if my friend had not signed up
for doterra i would not have gone down
the rabbit hole
i would not have been binge watching
them on thursday i would not have done
that that
that uh video that video would have
happened i wouldn't have missed the play
date
i wouldn't i might have still missed the
plane because that's not the reason i
missed the play date but if i hadn't
also missed the play
that's the other thing weaving in then i
wouldn't have had this conversa i
wouldn't have been where i was today i
wouldn't have had this conversation
and so what is coming out of this is
i've invited my siblings we'll see if my
brother comes my sisters agreed
to do a solution raising on essential
oils
essentially it was not a topic that i
would normally cover with a solution
raising but i'm like if they are
something that people want and they seem
to be what what does that look like and
i happen to have someone who's in the
business but also
a solution crazy like she's she's in
she's a capitalist business
in in essential oils and yet she is here
to do good and she's
she's waking up more and more to to the
capitalism in its current iteration is
broken
and so i was like there's something
asking there's a reason i'm asking her
to be part of it i don't actually know
what the outcome is going to be
and it might just be the three of us
having a conversation with my brother
then i also had the urge
to invite this friend of mine because it
might be that my sister and her get a
connection
it might be that there's something
coming out like this friend of mine
who's involved in a resource-based
economy is here to do good but is
also chronically ill because a lot of us
are chronically ill who are here to
do good because we've known about
all the stuff that's wrong on the planet
for so long and
it's a lot and so there's some reason
this conversation's coming together and
we just had my sister and i said two
hour conversation where she talked about
her
future vision it was the most healing
conversation we've had in two years
maybe even three or four years even when
we were talking
and it's like we had the falling out for
a reason we both have grown and it's
like we both are like
closer back to together like not in a
relationship-wise but in lifestyle-wise
it's like i came kind of a little bit
more over to her side
more understanding through game b just
less rigidity towards my vision through
game b
that i might have been able to hold to
have if we had to maintain that
relationship for that year and a half
like i needed her not in my life for
that for sure
i still i'm gonna get triggered by her
constantly um
but like my friend got involved in
essential oils i wouldn't have had this
conversation with my sister i wouldn't
be having the solution raising i
wouldn't be connecting with these
anti-mlmrs who have a real platform some
of them
on like tens of thousands of followers
on youtube and instagram as opposed to
200. i love you guys i love the people
who've been here
who who are here and who come to
solution raisings and
show up on camera i am more fond of my
200 subscribers than most people are of
their
their tens of thousands but i'm here to
do big things in the world
and if when i put an id out there it
actually had something happen
that'd be awesome so i'm not attached to
the outcome the more i'm attached to an
outcome the less it actually happens
it's like the one thing that won't
happen is the outcome i was attached to
so why be attached
just like i'm told to have the solution
raising on essential oils
invite my sister invite my friend invite
my brother
schedule it whoever shows up who shows
up and we'll see what happens
but i wanted to share everything that
went into that and i'm sure i'm missing
so much out because i can't this would
be hours long just to dissect that one
thing
all of the things that came up during
the walk what is coming out with this
conversation on youtube
i wouldn't think that my friend joining
an essential oil company
would have a learning for me for my
sister for our relationship for the
planet possibly
but it does because that's how the
universe works it is here to teach you
it is here to guide you
and everything is unfolding and it's
perfect time and way
and i'm here to showcase my little piece
of that so hopefully you can find your
little piece of that
thank you